Guide to the City and Regional Planning Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- City Planning Subject Files, 1873-2000; Series III
  - Housing
    - Surveys
      - Prediction Of The Incidence Of Urban Residential Blight, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Urban Development: The Government Role
      - Building A Better America, Undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Housing And Urban Development '67, Undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - A New Partnership To Conserve America's Communities, 1978 March (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Industrial Areas
    - Anatomy Of Industry, Minneapolis, 1960, 1960 August (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Bibliography Of Published Information On Planned Industrial Districts and Industrial Parks, 1962 February (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Characteristics of 63 Modern Industrial Plants, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Economic Development And Land Use In Westchester County, 1955-1975, 1960 August (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Fredella Village, Vicksburg, Mississippi, Undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Industrial Land Use Requirements For The Fresno-Clovis Metropolitan Area, 1963 September (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - The Industrial Plant in Connecticut, 1966 November (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Land For Industrial Growth, Minneapolis 1959, 1960 March (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Land For Industry, 1955 April (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Major Industrial Construction In Connecticut, 1970 January (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Off-Rail Industrial Lands Plans Study, 1961 October (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Location Factors
    - Annals Of The Association Of American Geographers, 1964 June (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Community Size And Agglomeration Of Trade Service And Other Locally Oriented Industries, 1966 September (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - The Labor Factor In Plant Location in Michigan, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Manufacturing Costs And The Comparative Advantage Of United States Regions, 1963 April (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Planning The Airport Industrial Park, 1965 September (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Taxation And Industrial Location In Michigan, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Urban Growth And Import Substitution In The Service Industries, 1966 September (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Intergovernmental Relations
    - Challenges And Choices, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Intergovernmental Challenges In New England, 1965 July (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Land For Development
    - Idle Land In An Urbanizing Area: The Delaware Experience, 1963 July (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Land Developability in Dade County, Florida, 1960 September (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Land Development, 1963 August (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - A Land Speculation Model: The Role Of The Property Tax As A Constraint To Urban Sprawl, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - New Life For Dead Lands, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Regional Site Map in the Six Counties Of New Jersey, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - The Rural Society In Transition, 1966 April (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Suburban Development In Metropolitan Northern Delawar e, 1966 June (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1963 Survey Of Vacant Land In The City Of Chicago, 1964 October (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Land Use
    - Commercial Areas
      - Commercial Activity Location Model, 1967 January (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - The Concept Of Mass In Intra-Urban Shopping, 1967 October (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - A Model Of Locational Equilibrium For Retail Trade, 1964 October (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Patterns And Trends Of Chicago's Outlying Business Centers, 1942 February (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Preliminary Results 1961 Shopping Center Study, 1962 January (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Probabilistic Analysis Of Consumer Spatial Behavior, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Shopping Center Survey Manual, 1968 February (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Space Use Analysis Of Major Commercial Centers, 1965 October (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Suburban Business Centers, 1961 September (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Public
      - Educational, Institutional And Administrative Facilities And The Land Use In New Jersey, 1965 January (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Federal Installations And The Land Use Pattern In New Jersey, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Public Land And Facilities, Nothern Virginia Region, 1962 September (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - A Study Of Land Ownership, Circa 1963 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Residential
      - Land Disposal Policy In New York City, 1965 August (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Residential Development Of New Jersey: A Regional Approach, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Government
    - Approaches To Governmental Organization For Metropolitan Areas, 1964 June (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Reference Handbook On Metropolitan Areas, Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Programs
    - New Haven Development Guide, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - New York City's Renewal Strategy, 1965 December (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Urban Renewal In Andover, Massachusetts, 1962 March (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood Plans
    - Encyclopédie De L'Urbanisme, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Downtown
      - Boston, Proposals For Downtown Boston, 1940 October (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - North Carolina, Legal Considerations In Central Business District Planning And Development, 1965 March (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Philadelphia
        - Focus: The Seventies, 1970 April (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Market Easy Study 1964 (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Proposals For Downtown Philadelphia, Undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Rhode Island
        - The Federal Hill Area, 1964 May (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Downtown Providence 1970, 1961 May (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - New England
    - A Decade Of Regional Planning In New England, 1943 June (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Open Space
    - Breathing Space, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Green Acres Procedural Guide, 1965 January (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Green Acres, Third Annual Report, 1965 January (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - The Green Belts, 1962-1962 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Law Of Open Space In The National Capital Region, 1965 September (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - A Matter Of Environment, Undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Open Lands Projects, 1964 August (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Open Space Action Analysis, 1967 January (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Open Space For Human Needs, Undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Open Space For Our Citified Country, 1964 January (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Open Space In The Penjerdel Region, Now or Never, 1963 March (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Open-Space Land Program Guide, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Open Space Program For Westchester County, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - A Plan For Open Space In Suffolk County, 1964 May (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Recreational Open Space Priorities, Undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Toward Land And Water For 1980, 1962 September (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - The Urban Setting: Man's Need For Open Space, 1980 March (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Population, Mobility and Migration
    - Geographical And Social Mobility, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - The Cost Of Geographic Mobility, 1964 April (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - The Impact Of Housing Patterns On Job Opportunities, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Poverty Programs
    - Community Action Program Management Guide, 1968 August (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Presentation, volume 1, 1965 April (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Upward Bound, policy guidelines and application, 1965 December (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Public Finance
    - Chart Book on Governmental Finances and Employment, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Handbook Of State And Local Government Finance, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - The Responsiveness Of State Tax Revenue To Economic Growth, 1967 November (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - State Planning Agencies
      - Massachusetts
        - Annual Report Of The State Planning Board, 1936 November-1937 November, 1939, 1941 November (Box 37, Folder 1-4)
        - Annual Report For The Year Ending November 30, 1942, 1942 November (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - New York
        - Annual Report Of The State Planning Council For The State Planning Division, 1936-1937, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 6-8)
      - Rhode Island
        - Development Council Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
        - Recreation In Rhode Island, 1936-1937 (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Rhode Island Planning Conference, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Sixth Annual Report Of The State Planning Board (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - Statewide Planning Program Annual Report, 1968 April (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - Student Faculty Projects and Publications-Yale
          - City Planning At Yale, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 15)
          - Crisis, Harvard Graduate School Of Design, Undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - River Programs
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement, volume 2-Exhibits, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rivers and Regionalism in New England, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Roadsides
    - The Scenic Route, A Guide For The Designation Of An Official Scenic Highway (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Shopping Centers
    - A Selected And Annotated Bibliography On The Planned Shopping Center, 1960 February (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Shopping Center Effects On Central Business Districts, 1965 October (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Shopping Centers In The Detroit Region, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 12-14)
    - Survey And Analysis Of Shopping Centers In A Suburban County, 1963 August (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Swedish Shopping Centers, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Social and Economic Data
    - Massachusetts
      - Jamaica Plain Study, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Survey Of Boston Metropolitan District And Adjacent Areas, 1940 June (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - New York
      - Duchess County Data Book, 1962 January (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - States and Regions
      - General Facts About Kentucky, 1966 March (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - New England Socio-Economic and Economic Characteristics Profile, 1940-1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Upper Midwest Urban Change In The 1960's, 1968 June (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - United States
      - Human Conservation: The Story Of Our Wasted Resources, 1943 March (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Key To The Great Society-Social Development, Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 200 Million Americans, 1967 November (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Special Districts and Authorities
    - A Selected Bibliography On Special Districts And Authorities In The United States, 1968 June (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Suburbs
    - Decentralization: What Is It doing To Our Cities?, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - The Present And Ultimate Effect Of Decentralization Upon American Cities, Undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Taxation
    - Government Guaranteed Annual Income And The Negative Income Tax, 1967 August (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Intergovernmental Cooperation In Tax Administration, 1961 June (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - State Expenditure Controls: An Evaluation, 1965 October (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Traffic
    - Engineering
      - Some Aspects Of The Urban Traffic Assignment Problem, 1963 July (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Traffic Regulation In Small Cities, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Surveys
      - Statistics With Applications To Highway Traffic Analyses, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Transportation Planning
    - An Analysis Of Metropolitan Transportation Systems, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Are We Willing To Pay For Congestion-Free Transportation?, 1964 January (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - A Form For Movement Through Pluralistic Cities, 1962 April (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Coordination Of Service--Basis For An Improved National Transportation System, 1964 November (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Decision Criteria In The Development Of A Statewide Transportation System, 1966 June (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - The Demand For Transportation Services In A Growing Economy, 1962 December (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Development And Testing Of A Gravity Model For The Providence Metropolitan Area, 1966 May (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - The Economics And Importance Of Speed, 1966 October (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - The Effect Of Density On Urban Transportation Requirements, 1963 January (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - The Effect Of Transportation On Residential Location, 1964 April (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Lower Manhattan, 1963 November (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - The Lower Manhattan Plan, Undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Maintaining Mobility, 1981 June (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - A Model-Choice Model--Description of Basic Concepts, 1966 December (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - A Model Split Model For Forecasting Future Transit Usage In The Providence Metropolitan Area, 1966 May (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Optimizing Comon Carrier Terminal Locations, 1966 March (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Optimizing Transportation Potential, 1966 September (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - A Reconnaissance Of The Tri-State Region, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - A Report On Urban Transportation Model, Some Progress And Some Problems, 1962 June (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - The Revolution in Information Processing Applied To Transportation, 1964 July (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Statewide Transportation Planning: A Key Element In Environmental Design, 1966 November (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - A Survey Of Factors Which Affect Transportation Cost, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - System Configurations In Urban Transportation Planning, 1964 January (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Technical Bulletin, 1967 October (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Technical Studies In Transportation: Transportation Cost Finding, 1963 December (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Toward A Transportation Policy For Manhattan, 1965 November (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Traffic On The Urban Scene-Concepts And Policies, 1966 December (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Transportation And Urban Goals For Urban Transportation, 1967 April (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Transportation Developments, Cities, And Planning, 1965 April (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Transportation For Future Urban Communities; A Study Prospectus, 1961 August (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Trip Length Variations Within Urban Areas, 1966 June (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Value Of Time, Choice Of Mode, And The Subsidy Issue In Urban Transportation, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Transportation Project
      - Washington-Boston Corridor
        - The Abstract Mode Model: Theory And Measurement, 1966 June (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - Analysis Of A Market Split Model, 1967 April (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Approaches to The Model Split: Intercity Transportation, 1967 February (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Description Of The Area System For The Northeast Corridor, 1965 December (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Description Of Projections Of Natural Population Increase And Labor Force, 1965 October (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Method For The Initial Superdistrict Projections Of Northeast Corridor Population, Employment And Income, 1966 August (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - A Model Of Output And Employment In Contract Construction In The Northeast Corridor Region, 1966 February (Box 39, Folder 19)
        - A Transport Improvement Problem Transformable To A Best-Path Problem, 1967 April (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Underdeveloped Nations
    - Cost-Benefit Analysis Of Improved Housing: A Case Study, 1965 October (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Housing And Development: Two Excerpts, 1966 April (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Housing And Productivity Casuality And Measurement, 1966 August (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - A Housing Model For Developing Economics: A Note On The Optimal Rent Subsidy, 1966 June (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Housing--Step-Child Of Development, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - International Standard Classification Of Community Development Activities, 1966 June (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Squatter Housing: Criteria For Development, Directions For Policy, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - The Super-Duper Texas Of The Year 2000, 1968 September (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Urbanization: Development Policies and Planning, Circa 1968 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Urban Design
    - Honor Awards For Design Excellence, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Public Housing Administration Honor Awards For Design Excellence (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - A Preliminary Study/Preserving The Architectural Character Of A Neighborhood, 1954 November (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Urban Development Corporation
    - The New York State Urban Development Corporation Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
  - Urban Pathology
    - The Homeless Man On Skid Row, 1961 September (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Institute For Community Development, 1963 August (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Philadelphia's Skid Row: A Demonstration In Human Renewal, Undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal
    - Are Urban Renewal Programs For Large Cities Only?, Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Conservation Techniques
      - A Step-By-Step Procedure For Processing Federal Housing Administration Section 220 Home Loans, 1964 January (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - County And Regional Programs
      - Technical reports for The Northeastern New Jersey Regional Urban Renewal Survey, 1963 May (Box 40, Folder 20-21)
    - Economics
      - Efficiency In Public Urban Renewal Expenditures Through Benefit-Cost Analysis, Undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Efficiency In Public Urban Renewal Expenditures Through Capital Budgeting, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Joint Press Release, 1965 April (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Public Policies In Urban Renewal: An Economic Analysis Of Justifications and Effects, Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - The Scope And Financing Of Urban Renewal And Development, 1953 April (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Summary Of Feasibility Of Benefit-Cost Applications In Urban Renewal, 1968 August (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Home Builders Guide To Urban Renewal, Undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Land Economics
      - The Allocation Of Urban Space: Mechanism For Deciding Among The Claims Of The Various Uses, Undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Economic Survey Of the Land Uses Of Evanston, Illinois, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - The Economic Survey Of The Land Uses Of Arlington County Virginia, 1951 September (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Effects Of Public Investments On Urban Land Values, 1966 July (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Price Management Of Building Sites In The United States-A Comparison Among Metropolitan Areas, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Public Policy And The Space Economy Of The City, Undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Master Plan Of Parks, 1941 January (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Model Cities
      - Cities That Show That Rehabilitation Can Work, 1965 September (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Improving Neighborhoods, 1967 April (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Improving The Quality Of Urban Life, 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
      - Model City Planning Grant Application, Omaha, Nebraska, 1968 April (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Neighborhood Conservation Agencies
      - Conservation And Rehabilitation, Undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Housing, Preservation And Development Of In REM Buildings, 1980 May (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - An Interim Report On Neighborhood Conservation In New York City, 1963 June (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Neighborhood Renewal Program
      - New York
        - Central Syracuse, Part 1 Development Policies And Objectives, 1964 October (Box 41, Folder 20)
        - Central Syracuse, Part 2: Recommended Renewal Action, 1965 July (Box 41, Folder 21)
        - A Plan For The Future City Of Gloversville, New York, 1963 September (Box 41, Folder 22)
        - The Plan For Downtown Ithaca, 1962 July (Box 41, Folder 23)
        - Report On Existing Conditions For Morningside Heights Neighborhood Renewal Area, 1961 August (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - South End General Neighborhood Renewal Plan, Undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Philadelphia
        - Market Street East, 1966 June (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Rhode Island
        - Thames Street Renewal Area, Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - The Politics Of Urban Renewal: Suggestions For A Conceptual Scheme, 1961 September (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Project Plans
      - Philadelphia
        - Center City Area Redevelopment Area Plan, 1963 February (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Haddington Redevelopment Area Plan, 1962 March (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Independence Mall Urban Renewal Area, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Market West Center City Redevelopment Area, 1965 June (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Nicetown Redevelopment Area Plan, 1965 October (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - North Allen Plan, 1965 February (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - Philadelphia Redevelopment Areas, 1967 February (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Redevelopment Area Number 8 (Old City), 1948 January (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - San Francisco
        - The Fillmore Center, 1963 January (Box 42, Folder 12)
        - Information Summary Butchertown Redevelopment Project Area, 1966 April (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - The Redevelopment Plan For The Golden Gateway, 1959 April (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - Two Renewal Projects Set A New Standard Of Quality In Urban Housing Design, 1964 February (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Public Housing In England: An Inquiry Into Selected Management Issues, 1964 March (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Relocation-Commercial
      - Attitude Survey Of Businessmen In The Queensgate II Project Area, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Comparative Mortality Experience Of Small Business In Four Chicago Communities, 1966 November (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Statistical Summary Of Programs, 1982 March (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Workable Program
      - Neighborhood Analysis, 1958 March (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - A Review Of Progress Under The Workable Program For Community Improvement, 1962 Aug, 1966-1968 June (Box 42, Folder 21-23)
  - War And Post-War Planning-Great Britain
    - Association For Planning And Regional Reconstruction, 1944 February-1945 June (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Living In Cities, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Waterfront Development
    - Agenda For Action-Recommendations From 1984 Waterfront Conference, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Alexandria's Waterfront, 1968 July (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Buffalo: Waterfront, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - The Changing Harborfront, 1966 March (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - California
      - Municipal, State and Federal Programs Affecting San Francisco Bay, 1966 June (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Progress Report: San Francisco Bay Conservation and Development Commission (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Review Of Barrier Proposals For San Francisco Bay, 1968 April (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - San Francisco Bay Plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Waterfront Development-A Planning Approach, 1963 November (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Waterfront Renewal, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Zoning
    - Handbook
      - Zoning Handbook-Metropolitan Dade County, Florida, 1965 September (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Zoning In New York State: A Guide To The Preparation Of Zoning Ordinances, 1950, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 14-15)
    - Land Use Control
      - Height Limits In Northeastern San Francisco, 1963 October (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Land Use Contrasts In A Border Econom y, 1964 June (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Land Use Controls, Undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Open Space Option, 1967 February (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Requiem For Zoning, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Law
      - Urban Zoning In New Hampshire, 1936 April (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Non Urban
      - Development Controls: A County Comprehensive Plan Study, Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Ordinances
      - Housing Quality: A Program For Zoning Reform, Circa 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Remarks Of Marie C. McGuire, 1964 October (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Some Facts About Federal Housing Administration Housing For The Elderly, Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Zoning in New Jersey, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Zoning In Philadelphia, 1966 March (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Zoning Primer, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 8)